* Product
    
    Zapier Automation Platform
    --------------------------
    
    No-code automation across 7,000+ apps
    
    PRODUCTS
    --------

    CAPABILITIES
    ------------

    What's new
    
    * * *
    
    * [CanvasBeta
        
        Plan and map your workflows with AI](https://zapier.com/canvas)
    * [AI ChatbotBeta
        
        Answer customer questions with AI chatbots](https://zapier.com/ai/chatbot)
    * [CentralBeta
        
        Create your own AI bots for any task](https://zapier.com/central)

* Solutions
    
    Solutions
    ---------
    
    How Zapier can help you automate your work across teams
    
    By team
    -------

    By app
    ------
    
    * [
        
        Salesforce](https://zapier.com/apps/salesforce/integrations)
    * [
        
        HubSpot](https://zapier.com/apps/hubspot/integrations)
    * [
        
        Slack](https://zapier.com/apps/slack/integrations)
    * [
        
        OpenAI](https://zapier.com/apps/openai/integrations)
    * [
        
        Microsoft Dynamics CRM](https://zapier.com/apps/microsoft-dynamics-crm/integrations)
    * [
        
        Microsoft Teams](https://zapier.com/apps/microsoft-teams/integrations)
    * [
        
        Zendesk](https://zapier.com/apps/zendesk/integrations)
    * [
        
        Jira Software Cloud](https://zapier.com/apps/jira-software-cloud/integrations)
    * [
        
        Marketo](https://zapier.com/apps/marketo/integrations)
    
    By use case
    -----------

    See how Zapier can take your RevOps and GTM engine to the next level
    
    * * *
    
    Zapier for
    ----------

    * * *

* Resources
    
    * By team

        -----------

    * Learn more

        --------------

    * Get help

        ------------

    Create your first Zap with ease
    
    * * *
    
    Developer resources
    -------------------

    * * *

Loading

Zapier Privacy Statement
------------------------

Update Notice: This Zapier Privacy Statement is posted on September 1, 2023, and is effective October 1, 2023. Your continued use of the Site and Services automatically constitutes your acceptance of this updated Statement. You may review the prior version of the Zapier Privacy Statement [here](https://res.cloudinary.com/zapier-media/image/upload/v1693601137/Legal/Zapier_Privacy_Policy-prior_version_rwjddl.pdf). This updated Zapier Privacy Statement completely replaces all previous versions.

**Supplemental Privacy Statements**

What this Statement Covers
--------------------------

This Zapier Privacy Statement (“Privacy Statement”) describes how Zapier, Inc. and our affiliated entities collect, use, process, and share your personally identifiable information. This Statement describes your choices regarding any applicable rights of access, deletion, and correction of your personal information. Where we refer to “information” in this Privacy Statement, it means any information that relates to an identified person.

This Privacy Statement applies to [zapier.com](https://zapier.com/), [community.zapier.com](https://community.zapier.com/) and [experts.zapier.com/](https://zapier.com/experts), and any other website that links to this Statement (the “Site”). This Privacy Statement also applies to the information that we collect through the services we offer or our developer programs (the Zapier developer platform and the Zapier services, we refer to as “Services”), communities, through marketing and customer engagement, branded social media pages.

This Privacy Statement does not apply to the information we collect about employees (our employment policies apply) or job applicants (our [Applicant Privacy Statement applies](https://zapier.com/privacy/applicant-privacy-statement)). This Privacy Statement also does not apply to information collected by third parties, like third-party websites, social media platforms or accounts, third-party service providers, or other third-party services or applications that integrate with our Services. This Privacy Statement also does not apply to any information that is not personally identifiable, like aggregated or anonymous information.

We may update this Privacy Statement from time to time and provide notice to you as described below in the section titled “Notice of Changes.”

Our Services are not directed at children under the age of 16, and we do not knowingly collect information from individuals under the age of 16. If you are under the age of 16, you may not use the Services or provide your information to us through the Site or otherwise.

If you are a citizen of Switzerland, the United Kingdom, or a country in the European Economic Area, we describe additional rights you may have in the [European Privacy Rights](https://zapier.com/privacy/european-privacy-rights) statement. If you are a California resident, we describe additional rights you may have in the [California Privacy Rights](https://zapier.com/privacy/california-privacy-rights) statement.

---

Personal Information We Collect
-------------------------------

We collect or receive information in the ways we describe in this section.

Categories of Information We Collect

* Information You Provide Us
* When You Create an Account
* Content or Information You Provide in the Services
* Content You Provide Through Our Site
* Support Channels or Communities
* Marketing Information
* Partner Program
* Payment Processing Information
* Technical, Device, and Connection Information
* Cookies and Other Tracking Technology
* Other Information Sources

**Information You Provide Us**: When you sign up to create an account in the Service, download content from the Site, fill out a form or survey or respond to communications, you provide us with information like your name, email address, address, company, phone number or other information. When you register for a community or a partner program, we collect account registration information like your name, email address, address, company, phone number, or other information. You may provide comments, communications, feedback, ratings, or other information when you use the Services or any of our communities or partner programs.

**When You Create an Account**: When you create an account, you provide us with your account registration and profile information (name, email address, company, and similar information). We automatically track certain information about your use of the Services, partner programs, or communities. We collect information about you when you login and how you interact with the Services, the features you use, clicks, log information about your use of the Services, and how you interact with other users. We describe the information we collect through the Services in more detail in [Zapier Services](https://zapier.com/privacy/zapier-services) statement.

**Content or Information You Provide in the Services**: The Services allow you to create connections or integrations between the third-party applications you use. When you use the Services, information or content is transferred from one application to another application. We collect the information that is transferred between the third-party applications. We describe the information we collect through your use of the Services in more detail in the [Zapier Services](https://zapier.com/privacy/zapier-services) statement. Other users may provide information about individuals when they submit content or information through the Services. For example, if a user sets up a Zap that allows automated calendaring, that user will share information about the individuals they schedule meetings with via the Zap. Users may also provide information about their teammates, including name and email address, to invite teammates to use the Services. Similarly, an administrator may provide your contact information if they designate you as a user, the billing contact, technical contact, or administrator. You or your administrator may integrate the Services with third-party applications. In such case, we will receive information that allows us to identify your account within the third-party applications (like name, email address, phone number, tokens, or other identifying information), the log data, content, and device information. The information or content we receive from your organization is subject to your organization’s privacy policies. When you integrate our Services with a third-party application, the information we receive depends on the settings, permissions, and privacy Statement controlled by that third-party application.

**Content You Provide Through Our Site**: If the Site or our social media platform pages allow you to upload content or information, we will collect the content or information you upload. For example, when you provide feedback, participate in any interactive features, surveys, contests, promotions, sweepstakes, activities, or events, you may provide us information or content.

**Information You Provide Through Support Channels or Communities**: You may provide information or content to us through the customer support or chat functionality we make available on the Site, in the Services, or other sites that we control. When you engage with our support team, in addition to your account information, we may ask you to provide additional information about your issue, which may include information about your technology, software, internet connection, or screenshots. To submit information to a community site, we may require you to create an account within the community (we will collect your account registration information like name, email, company, address, and phone number). If you have an account in the Services, we will associate your community membership and activities with your Services account. As a community member, you and other members may submit questions, provide answers, engage with members through chat or comments, create content or webinars to share with the community, or solicit feedback or help from other community members.

**Marketing Information**: We receive information about you directly from you when you engage with the Site and automatically when you engage with the Site or open or click the emails we send you (See Information You Provide Us and Cookies and Other Tracking Technology). We receive information from third-party sources like lead generation providers, content sponsors, event sponsors, or social media platforms. The information we collect from third-party sources may include marketing or demographic information, contact information (name, email, company, address, job title), information about your profile on those platforms, or information about purchasing intent. We may combine this information with the information we collect.

**Partner Programs**: We have several partner programs that we make available: our developer platform program (which allows third-party application providers to build integrations to Zapier) and our expert program (which connects experts who help our customers set up and use the Services). Partners may also help us to market and promote our Services, generate leads, or they may resell our Services. We may add partner programs in the future. Through partner programs, we collect account registration information (like name, email address, company, and phone number), information about an individual’s technical skill set, comments, questions or feedback, rating or ranking information, images, content, or other information you provide. We may also receive information from our partners (like business contact information, address, job title, email address, or phone number). We will combine the information you provide and the information we receive with your account information.

**Payment Processing Information**: When you create a paid account within the Services or otherwise initiate a transaction with us, we will use a third-party payment processor to process the payment. We do not collect your credit card number, expiration date, or pin number. The transaction details we retain are those details that allow us to verify that you paid for the Services or transaction, including price, currency, date of payment, payment method, name, and account name. We will combine that information with your account information.

**Technical, Device, and Connection Information**: When you use the Services or interact with our Site, we automatically collect information about the device you use to access the Site or Services. When you interact with our branded social media sites, the social media platform automatically collects information and provides it to us. This information includes information that identifies you and connection type, settings, operating system, browser type, internet protocol (IP) address, URLs of referring/exit pages, device identifiers, and crash data.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technology**: We use cookies, web beacons, pixels, or other tracking technology on the Site and in the Services to provide functionality, personalize your experience and recognize you across services or devices. This information includes IP addresses, location, device type, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, click data, device-identifying data. We may combine this automatically collected information with other information that you provide us through other channels. You can learn more about our cookies in the Cookie Notice statement. When you interact with our social media sites, the social media platform automatically collects information and provides it to us.

**Other Information Sources**: We receive information about you from other sources like third-party service providers, public databases, and our business and channel partners. This information may include business contact information, address, job title, email address, phone number. We may combine this information with information we collect through other means.

How We Use Personal Information We Collect
------------------------------------------

We use the information we collect for the following purposes:

* to provide and support the Services,
* to improve the Services,
* to provide, support, and improve the Site, our partner programs, or communities,
* to process your requests,
* to process your payments or transactions,
* to provide you with information about our products and services,
* to combine information about you with other information we receive from third parties,
* to tailor the content or information that we provide to you,
* to protect the integrity or security of our business, the Site, Services, or third-party applications, or we may also use your information to: carry out our obligations, enforce our rights, comply with any legal obligation (including assisting our customer to comply with their legal obligations), where it is necessary for our legitimate interests, or to fulfill any other purpose for which you provided the information.

How We Share Personal Information
---------------------------------

We may share information when one of the following circumstances applies:

**With your Consent**: We may share your information with companies, organizations, and other third parties with your consent or to fulfill the purpose for which you provided the information.

**With our Partners**: We may share information with our partners (including resellers, referral, integration partners, experts in our community, or developer platform partners) for the purposes of the partnership agreement or to enable our partner programs.

**To Provide the Services, Partner Programs, or Communities**: We may share your information with your teammates, account administrators, billing, or technical account users. We will also share your information with third-party applications (at your direction or the direction of an account owner) when an account holder uses the Services. To deliver the Site, Services, partner programs, or communities, we may share your information with our service providers. If you participate in our partner programs or communities, we may share your information with other partners, community members, customers, or other users (like when you comment or share information, rate an expert, or express interest in a partner integration).

**For Business Purposes**: We provide information to vendors and services providers to help us provide the Site, Services, partner programs and communities, and for our business purposes. Examples of our service providers include hosting or infrastructure providers, chat widgets, helpdesk ticket providers, website hosts, customer relationship management providers, email providers, collaboration tools, and other service providers.

**To Market our Services or Partner Programs**: We may share information that you provide us with third-party service providers who help us market our Services or our partner programs. These service providers may provide virtual or live events, email marketing tools, sales engagement, or lead generation tools.

**For Corporate Transactions**: We may share personal data with actual or prospective acquirers, their representatives, and other relevant participants in, or during negotiations of, any sale, merger, acquisition, restructuring, divestiture, or change in control involving all or a portion of our business or assets, including in connection with a bankruptcy or similar proceedings. If we undergo a sale or corporate restructure, we may disclose information to a buyer or other successor in interest.

**For Legal Reasons**: We may share your information if we believe that it is necessary to comply with any court order, law, legal obligation, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request. We may share your information if we believe that it is necessary to enforce our rights (including, without limitation, our rights under the [Terms of Service](https://zapier.com/tos), [Terms of Use](https://zapier.com/tou), [Acceptable Use Statement](https://zapier.com/aup), or the [Zapier Platform Agreement](https://zapier.com/platform/tos)), or the rights of our customers, or users. We may share your information if we believe that it is necessary or appropriate to protect our rights or safety or the rights or safety of our customers, other users, partners, or service providers.

**With Third-Party Widgets**: If you click on a widget or social media feature, like the Twitter “tweet” button or Facebook “like” button, these widgets will share information with the widget provider (like IP address, the which page you are visiting on the Services and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function correctly).

Your Choices - Opting Out, Correcting or Accessing Your Information
-------------------------------------------------------------------

**Automatically Collected Information**: There are various resources available to you to manage cookies. In most modern browsers, you can block or delete cookies by clicking Settings > Privacy > Cookies. Instructions for blocking or deleting cookies in other browsers may be available in each browser’s privacy or help documentation. You can also disable or delete the stored data used by technology similar to cookies, such as Local Shared Objects or Flash cookies, by managing your browser’s “add-on settings” or visiting the website of its manufacturer. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies are used and stored and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.aboutcookies.org.](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) If you disable or refuse cookies, some parts of the Site or Service may then be inaccessible or not function properly. Please see the [Cookie Notice](https://zapier.com/privacy/cookie-notice) statement for more information about cookies.

**Our Marketing Activities**: If you would like to opt-out of receiving our marketing, you can opt-out by sending an opt-out email to [privacy@zapier.com](mailto:privacy@zapier.com). If we sent you a promotional email, you may opt-out by clicking the opt-out link at the bottom of the email or sending us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This-opt out does not apply to information necessary to deliver the Services, communities, or partner programs, like your account information or notices we send about the Services’ operation. If you have an account in the Services, you can manage your communication preferences (including opt-outs) in the settings page of your account profile.

**Services**. You can review and change your personal information in the Services by logging into the Service and visiting your account profile page. You may also send us an email at [privacy@zapier.com](mailto:privacy@zapier.com) to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. You can manage your communication preferences within the settings page of your account profile.

Data Security and Data Transfers
--------------------------------

**Data Security**. Zapier takes reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction, taking into account the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the personal data. However, no application, Internet, or email transmission is ever fully secure or error-free, and we do not guarantee the security of any personal information. You are also responsible for ensuring that your account and the passwords we provide you are protected.

**Data Storage and International Data Transfers**. Information that we collect from the Site will be transferred to, and processed in the United States and in any other country where Zapier or its affiliates, subsidiaries or third party service providers maintain facilities or personnel. These countries may have data protection laws that are different to the laws of your country (and, in some cases, may not be as protective). We follow applicable data protection laws when transferring personal data.If you are resident in or a visitor from the EEA, United Kingdom or Switzerland, we will protect your Personal Information when it is transferred outside of such locations by processing it in a territory which the European Commission has determined provides an adequate level of protection for Personal Information; or otherwise implementing appropriate safeguards to protect your Personal Information, including through the use of Standard Contractual Clauses or another lawful transfer mechanism approved by the European Commission.

For data transfers and storage of information we collect from your use of the Services, please refer to the detail in the [Zapier Services](https://zapier.com/privacy/zapier-services) statement.

EU-US Data Privacy Framework
----------------------------

Zapier complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF), and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF (the UK Extension) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over Zapier’s compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the Swiss-U.S. DPF, and the UK Extension.

Zapier has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to: (1) the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF; 2) the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF; and (3) the UK Extension with regard to the processing of personal data received from the UK in reliance on the UK Extension. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles, the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles or the UK Extension, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) Program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/)

In cases of onward transfer of personal information to third parties of data of EU, Swiss and UK individuals received pursuant to the EU-U.S. DPF, the Swiss-U.S DPF and the UK Extension, and in a manner inconsistent with the DPF Principals, Zapier will remain liable.

Dispute Resolution
------------------

You may direct any questions or complaints about this Privacy Statement to us by contacting us through the channels indicated below. Any disputes arising out of or related to this Privacy Statement will be handled in accordance with the dispute resolution process indicated in your contract with Zapier that refers to this Privacy Statement, if applicable. In the case of our customers or their users, that means our [Terms of Service](https://zapier.com/tos) or users of our developer platform, the [Zapier Platform Agreement](https://zapier.com/platform/tos). In the case of visitors to the Site, that means our [Website Terms of Use](https://zapier.com/tou).

In compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the Swiss-U.S. DPF, and the UK Extension, Zapier commits to refer unresolved complaints concerning our handling of personal data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF, the Swiss-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider based in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your DPF Principles-related complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your DPF Principles-related complaint to your satisfaction, please visit [https://www.jamsadr.com/DPF-Dispute-Resolution](https://www.jamsadr.com/DPF-Dispute-Resolution) for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you.

As a last resort, and in limited situations, EU, Swiss, and UK individuals may invoke binding arbitration from the E.U.-U.S. DPF Panel for complaints regarding DPF compliance not resolved by any of the DPF Mechanisms: [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/framework-article/ANNEX-I-introduction](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/framework-article/ANNEX-I-introduction).

Notice of Changes
-----------------

The Services, the Site, and our business may change from time to time. As a result, we may make changes to this Privacy Statement. We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Statement at any time and from time to time. If we make changes to this Privacy Statement, we will post the changes on this page and will indicate at the top of this page and the date these terms were last revised. If we make material changes, we will notify you through the Services user interface, as a pop up on the Site, in an email notification, or through other reasonable means. Your continued use of the Site or Services after the date any such notice constitutes your acceptance of the modifications.

---

Contacting Zapier
-----------------

If you have any questions or comments about this notice, how we collect and use your information, your choices or rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your rights, please do not hesitate to contact us at:

**Phone**: (877) 381-8743

**Email**: [privacy@zapier.com](mailto:privacy@zapier.com)

**Postal Address**:

Zapier, Inc.

Attn: Legal Department/Privacy

548 Market St. #62411, San Francisco, CA 94104-5401

Attn: Legal

**Change Log**
--------------

Date of Change: March 4, 2021

Description of Change: Updates made to the Privacy Statement to:

* Address legal and regulatory changes, including the removal of privacy shield references.
* Provide more detail about the categories of information we collect, the purposes for which we collect information, and the third parties with whom we share information.
* Restructured the Statement and the language to make the Statement easier for readers to navigate and understand.

### Follow us

© 2024 Zapier Inc.

* Manage cookies
